the moon express is rolling fast our shadows on
the window glass we're leaving campus in the
dark a single hopeful burn and spark the eight of
us a single pack we're never up
We're leaving just a day too soon beneath the
cold November moon. My mother's cold ultimatum
is just a fading, dying sound. We're heading to a
brand new place, a quiet, safe, and solid
ground. This is a sanctuary A house built on hell
A place where I can finally breathe A place where
I can just be still They're not just friends I'm
starting to see They're my chosen family This
basement is my sanctuary
I'm
Laura smiling at the door, she's happy that
we're here She doesn't see a burden, she doesn't
show a trace of fear A full house for
Thanksgiving, she says with so much joy She
doesn't see a broken thing, she just sees her
daughter's bones
This is a sanctuary A house built on a hill A place
where I can finally breathe A place where I can
just be still They're not just friends I'm
starting to see They're my chosen family This
basement is my sanctuary
My sanctuary We're safe We're home We're home